The	O
Spoken	B-ORG
Language	I-ORG
Systems	I-ORG
(	I-ORG
LSV	I-ORG
)	I-ORG
research	I-ORG
group	I-ORG
is	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Department	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Language	B-ORG
Science	I-ORG
&	I-ORG
Technology	I-ORG
and	O
the	O
Saarland	B-LOC
Informatics	I-LOC
Campus	I-LOC
.	O

Our	O
research	O
spans	O
a	O
variety	O
of	O
domains	O
in	O
the	O
area	O
of	O
computational	O
linguistics	O
and	O
machine	O
learning	O
.	O

Saarland	B-ORG
University	I-ORG
in	O
Saarbrücken	B-LOC
.	O
